http://www.poetrylibrary.org.uk/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Stay in the loop and register for email updates about events, competitions and all things poetry.
sign up now
You are hereHome
Privacy policy
The National Poetry Libary is managed by Southbank Centre which is a national arts organisation and a registered charity in England and Wales number 298909. Its trustee is Southbank Centre Limited, a company limited by guarantee registered in England and Wales number 2238415.
What information do we collect?
You give us your information when you sign up to receive email from from the National Poetry Library or Southbank Centre or when you buy/register for a Southbank Centre or National Poetry Library event ticket, make a purchase from our shop, buy something online or on our website, update your preferences on our website, tell us your story, make a donation or communicate with us.
Full privacy policy
Your rights
You have the following rights related to your personal data:
The right to request a copy of personal information held about you
The right to request that inaccuracies be corrected
The right to request us to stop processing your personal data
The right to withdraw consent
The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner's Office or Fundraising Regulator
Contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
Email us
Or write to us at: Data Protection, Customer Services, Southbank Centre, Belvedere Road, London. SE1 8XX
Facebook
Twitter
